Because honestly, if they would continue to say if or Hunter and we were playing a drinking game,
I would be drunk by now because I promise you they have not talked about the subject of this,
which would be the president. But let me tell you something that was so disturbing as I walked in
to this chamber today. As I prepared, I said, what is the crime? Because when you're talking
about impeachment, you're talking about high crimes or misdemeanors. And I can't seem to find
the crime. And honestly, no one has testified of what crime they believe the president of the
United States has committed. But when we started talking about things that look like evidence,
they want to act like they blind. They don't know what this is. These are our national secrets,
looks like in the shitter to me. This looks like more evidence of our national secrets,
say on a stage at Mar-a-Lago. When we're talking about somebody that's committed high crimes,
it's at least indictments. Let's say 32 counts related to unauthorized retention of national
security secrets. Seven counts related to obstructing the investigation. Three false statements.
One count of conspiracy to defraud the United States. Falsifying business records conspiracy
to defraud the United States. Two counts related to efforts to obstruct the vote certification
proceedings. One count of conspiracy to violate civil rights. 23 counts related to forgery or false
document statements. Eight counts related to soliciting. And that could go on because he's got
91 counts pending right now. But I will tell you what the president has been